i want to talk about something we don't talk enough about supreme have you heard of sleep
tourism yeah that's when people will just travel to go to sleep the whole time i have a friend that
does that i'm like you pay for a hotel just to go to sleep in yeah fascinating so sleep tourism
is exactly what you said is people traveling uh booking staycations to sleep at hotels and
basically hotels.com released a survey revealing that three out of four americans said they sleep
better at hotels why do you think that is it's just a new environment maybe it's a little bit more
relaxed i feel like your anxieties are so much lower if you're in a hotel like your safety isn't
as not even necessarily like your safety like your house isn't safe but it's like at least in your
house you know that if anything go down it's on you in a hotel you close that door you like all right
y'all whatever happens handle that how about naps are you a napper yes i just recently started taking
a nap i was not a napper until i started doing stand-up and i would have late sets you know like
i would have to do a 10 30 p.m set and it's like the day for me is done so i would like have to force
myself and i would take a 20 minute nap let me tell you something y'all don't sleep on them 20
well actually sleep on them 20 minutes laps because it'll help you that power nap is just enough and even
when you wake up from it you feel like a little groggy and you're just like why did i do that but then
it's like 20 minutes after that your body is like thank you
we are